# Getting Started with Create React App

This project was bootstrapped with [Create React App](https://github.com/facebook/create-react-app).

## Available Scripts

In the project directory, you can run:

### `npm start`

Runs the app in the development mode.\
Open [http://localhost:3000](http://localhost:3000) to view it in your browser.

The page will reload when you make changes.\
You may also see any lint errors in the console.

### `npm test`

Launches the test runner in the interactive watch mode.\
See the section about [running tests](https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/running-tests) for more information.

### `npm run build`

Builds the app for production to the `build` folder.\
It correctly bundles React in production mode and optimizes the build for the best performance.

The build is minified and the filenames include the hashes.\
Your app is ready to be deployed!

See the section about [deployment](https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/deployment) for more information.

### `npm run eject`

**Note: this is a one-way operation. Once you `eject`, you can't go back!**

If you aren't satisfied with the build tool and configuration choices, you can `eject` at any time. This command will remove the single build dependency from your project.

Instead, it will copy all the configuration files and the transitive dependencies (webpack, Babel, ESLint, etc) right into your project so you have full control over them. All of the commands except `eject` will still work, but they will point to the copied scripts so you can tweak them. At this point you're on your own.

You don't have to ever use `eject`. The curated feature set is suitable for small and middle deployments, and you shouldn't feel obligated to use this feature. However we understand that this tool wouldn't be useful if you couldn't customize it when you are ready for it.

## Learn More

You can learn more in the [Create React App documentation](https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/getting-started).

To learn React, check out the [React documentation](https://reactjs.org/).

### Code Splitting

This section has moved here: [https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/code-splitting](https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/code-splitting)

### Analyzing the Bundle Size

This section has moved here: [https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/analyzing-the-bundle-size](https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/analyzing-the-bundle-size)

### Making a Progressive Web App

This section has moved here: [https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/making-a-progressive-web-app](https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/making-a-progressive-web-app)

### Advanced Configuration

This section has moved here: [https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/advanced-configuration](https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/advanced-configuration)

### Deployment

This section has moved here: [https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/deployment](https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/deployment)

### `npm run build` fails to minify

This section has moved here: [https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/troubleshooting#npm-run-build-fails-to-minify](https://facebook.github.io/create-react-app/docs/troubleshooting#npm-run-build-fails-to-minify)
{
"question": "What does SOM stand for?",
"answer": "self-organizing map"
},
{
"question": "Repeat 5 Times: A wasted model is one which is never used by the SOM in its classification stage after training",
"answer": "A wasted model is one which is never used by the SOM in its classification stage after training"
},
{
"question": "A wasted model is one which is **\_** **\_** ** \_\_** ** \_**",
"answer": "never used by the SOM in its classification stage after training"
},
{
"question": "A wasted model is one which is **\_** **\_** ** \_\_**in its classification stage after training",
"answer": "never used by the SOM"
},
{
"question": " **\_** **\_** ** \_\_** ** \_** in its classification stage after training",
"answer": "A wasted model is one which is one which is never used by the som"
},
{
"question": " What is a wasted model",
"answer": "A wasted model is one which is one which is never used by the self-organizing map in its classification stage after training"
},
{
"question": "Repeat x5: They occur because of the topology preserving nature of the SOM",
"answer": "They occur because of the topology preserving nature of the SOM"
},
{
"question": "They occur because of the ** \_\_** \_**\_ \_** **\_ \_**M",
"answer": "topology preserving nature of the SOM"
},
{
"question": "Why do they occur?",
"answer": "They occur because of the topology preserving nature of the SOM"
},
{
"question": "What does BMU stand for?",
"answer": "Best Matching Unit."
},
{
"question": "REPEAT X5: As training progresses, nodes far from the Best Matching Unit that do not become BMUs remain outside the contracting Gaussian Learning envelope and thus stay undeveloped and unused.",
"answer": "As training progresses, nodes far from the Best Matching Unit that do not become BMUs remain outside the contracting Gaussian Learning envelope and thus stay undeveloped and unused."
},
{
"question": "As training progresses, **\_** **\_ \_** **\_ \_\_\_** \_**\_ \_** remain outside the contracting Gaussian Learning envelope and thus stay undeveloped and unused.",
"answer": "nodes far from the Best Matching Unit that do not become BMUs"
},
{
"question": "As training progresses nodes far from the Best Matching Unit (BMU) that do not become BMUs remain outside the contracting Gaussian Learning envelope \_ _ \_\_ _ \_ \_ \_ \_ \_ \_ ** ",
"answer": "and thus stay undeveloped and unused"
},
{
"question": "As training progresses nodes far from the Best Matching Unit (BMU) that do not become BMUs remain outside ** \***\*\_\_\_\*\*** **\_\_\_** **\_** **\_\_** and thus stay undeveloped and unused",
"answer": "The contracting Gaussian Learning envelope"
},
{
"question": "REPEAT x5: the U-Matrix of an SOM highlights the boundaries between the various distinct clusters in the SOM",
"answer": "highlights the boundaries between the various distinct clusters in the SOM."
},
{
"question": "the U-Matrix of an SOM**\_\_\_\_** **\_\_** **\_\_\_** **\_ \_** \_**\_",
"answer": "highlights the boundaries between the various distinct clusters in the SOM."
},
{
"question": "REPEAT X5: It normally is a simple binary matrix where the location of a 1 indicates a boundary and 0 a cluster interior ",
"answer": "It normally is a simple binary matrix where the location of a 1 indicates a boundary and 0 a cluster interior"
},
{
"question": "It normally is a \_\_** **\_** **\_\_** ",
"answer": "simple binary matrix"
},
{
"question": "where the location of a 1 **\*\***\*\***\*\***\_\_**\*\***\*\***\*\***",
"answer": "indicates a boundary and 0 a cluster interior."
},
{
"question": "**\*\*\*\***\_**\*\*\*\***indicates a boundary and 0 a cluster interior",
"answer": "where the location of a 1"
},
{
"question": "For a given trained SOM What is its U-Matrix?",
"answer": "The U-Matrix of an SOM highlights the boundaries between the various distinct clusters in the SOM. It normally is a simple binary matrix where the location of a 1 indicates a boundary and 0 a cluster interior."
},
{
"question": "REPEAT x5: SOMs can be unstable, affecting agents using them for classification and decision-making",
"answer": "SOMs can be unstable, affecting agents using them for classification and decision-making."
},
{
"question": "SOMs can be unstable, affecting**\*\*\*\***\_\_\_**\*\*\*\***",
"answer": "agents using them for classification and decision-making"
},
{
"question": "REPEAT x5: If the SOM model changes significantly, agents might need to unlearn established rules and develop new ones to match altered pattern recognitions, complicating the learning of appropriate responses in dynamic environments.",
"answer": " If the SOM model changes significantly, agents might need to unlearn established rules and develop new ones to match altered pattern recognitions, complicating the learning of appropriate responses in dynamic environments."
},
{
"question": "If the SOM model changes significantly, **\*\*\*\***\_\_**\*\*\*\***",
"answer": "agents might need to unlearn established rules"
},
{
"question": "and develop new ones to**\_\_\_\_**.",
"answer": "match altered pattern recognitions, complicating the learning of appropriate responses in dynamic environments"
},
{
"question": "REPEAT x5: For example, if a node initially identifying edible purple berries shifts to recognize poisonous red berries, the agent must adapt by changing its response from eating to avoiding",
"answer": "For example, if a node initially identifying edible purple berries shifts to recognize poisonous red berries, the agent must adapt by changing its response from eating to avoiding"
},
{
"question": "For example, if a node initially identifying edible purple berries shifts to recognize poisonous red berries**\*\*\*\***\_**\*\*\*\***",
"answer": "the agent must adapt by changing its response from eating to avoiding"
},
{
"question": "Stability can be a problem in SOM's. Give an example of how a trained SOM used for classifying might experience stability problems.",
"answer": "SOMs can be unstable, affecting agents using them for classification and decision-making. If the SOM model changes significantly, agents might need to unlearn established rules and develop new ones to match altered pattern recognitions, complicating the learning of appropriate responses in dynamic environments. For example, if a node initially identifying edible purple berries shifts to recognize poisonous red berries, the agent must adapt by changing its response from eating to avoiding"
},
